<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Investing Ninja</title>
    <description>Invest like a Ninja</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 19:35:17 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 19:35:17 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.5</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>The ‘Matrix’ Is Real: 5 Ways to Pull Yourself Free and Live More Prosperously</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;As millions of people flood cinemas to see the new “Matrix” movie, most of them will have no idea that in fact they’re plugged into a real-life matrix.
However, the real life matrix is not run by power-hungry computers; it has everything to do with the way people have been programmed since they were babies.
Before virtually everyone learns to talk, they become plugged into the Matrix of Fear and Limitation.
Another name for it is the Culture of Lack Programming, or the Poverty Consciousness.
In too many cases, it’s keeping people living paycheck to paycheck and building a mountain of debt instead of a nest egg for the future.
They work for money, instead of money working for them, as it’s supposed to be.
These people often have to take additional jobs and end up losing their freedom – and that has tremendous impact on them:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They become needy. Their self-esteem takes a dive, because they must rely on their jobs, their bosses and perhaps others They have no time or energy to spend with their partners or children. Love life? Not a chance. In fact, they’re under so much stress, they’re more likely to take it out on their partner and children, causing everyone to suffer more. This often causes families to split apart They don’t see a way out of this spiral, and it seems to only get worse. This causes them to lose hope; their work suffers, and their life becomes a struggle&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hold on, though, because there is hope.
Here are five things people can do to get back in control of their lives and start breaking free from the Matrix:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stop associating with negative people. Being with complainers and gossipers, well, let’s just say it has a greater effect than people realize. Instead, surround yourself with positive, optimistic people who will leave you uplifted and full of hope. Stop complaining yourself. It’s really true what they say, that “what you focus on expands.” When you draw your attention to what’s not working in your life, you get a whole lot more of it. Instead, get into the habit of focusing on what IS going right in your life, and being grateful for that. You’ll start getting more things to be happy about. Keep your TV off (or sell it) and don’t read or listen to any “news” programs. All they do is promote fear and get people to focus on what’s not working. We already talked about how harmful that is to each of us. The media also gets people to focus on what’s not right about themselves (mainly through commercials), doing tremendous damage to their self-image, which has major impact on what they believe they can achieve. Become a life-long learner. When you read books and listen to tapes on personal development, you become a better person. That helps you realize just how much power you have and you make better decisions. It’s also true when they say that “problems are never solved at the level of thinking that created them.” Listen to an inspirational tape a day and you’ll quickly rise above what previously seemed like insurmountable problems. You’ll also counter-act a lot of the negative programming you’re exposed to dozens of times every day. Become a critical thinker. You’ve already limited your exposure to negative, harmful messages from the people around you, the media and even your own self-talk. Yet you may not be able to prevent it all from affecting you. For example, much of the programming you’ve “learned” came from your parents, and you probably don’t want to break all ties to your family. And because almost all your Poverty Consciousness beliefs are based on habits you’ve had for perhaps decades, it will take serious work to counteract this programming. By being super-critical of your own thoughts, the movies you watch and even the songs you hear, you can at least reject the influences you’re aware of that keep people down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taking these five steps to heart will enable you to change your life and your financial circumstances, actually as quickly and to the extent that you embrace them.
In truth it always has been within your power to determine how wealthy you are, and it is your birthright to be rich.
By replacing the old habits and beliefs that don’t serve you, and making these five steps the foundation for your new habits and actions, you’ll be able to pull yourself from the Matrix of Fear and Limitation, and instead be free, living a life of prosperity and abundance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dan Klatt&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/tutorial/2019/06/19/the-matrix-is-real-5-ways-to-pull-yourself-free-and-live-more-prosperously.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/tutorial/2019/06/19/the-matrix-is-real-5-ways-to-pull-yourself-free-and-live-more-prosperously.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Guide to FX Trading Corp</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-is-fx-trading-corporation&quot;&gt;What is FX Trading Corporation?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FX Trading Corporation is an MLM Crypto Trading company located in South Korea, which makes money from mining companies in various places around the world with Bitcoin, Etherium, Bitcoin in cash, Litecoin, etc. They have developed proprietary software called “BOT-FX” which perform this automated trading operations which can give up to 2.5% or daily return to your investment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With FX Trading Corp, There are few ways that you can earn money. which is ROI Commissions, Referral Commissions, and Residual Commissions. Also, we have personally tested the site and we were able to get the capital we invested with more than 100% return and with the recent changes of the company policies we can assure about the site and the money we invest with them as they are more focusing on the sustainability of the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;roi-commissions&quot;&gt;ROI Commissions&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To earn ROI Commissions, all you have to do is to make an investment in what of the packages they offer in the site and with those packages, you will earn up to 2.5% within 200 days (from Monday to Friday). Below is the breakdown of each level of investment that the company has to offer;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/post-guide-to-fxtradingcorp/investing-plans.png&quot; alt=&quot;Investment Plans&quot; title=&quot;Investment Plans&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based on the plan you have chosen, you will get daily profit up to 2.5% (As per our own experience, daily profit is within 1% – 2%) and assume you have invested on a BOT1000 plan and based on the platform performance (bots) of the day, daily profit percentage is 1.3%, you will get $13 as your profit to your account by the end of the day (Bots operations for the day is ending at 12:00 PM and your account is updating with the profit at 03:00 AM South’s Korea time daily from Monday to Friday).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;referral-commissions&quot;&gt;Referral Commissions&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are a few ways that you can earn commissions with the referrals you have introduced to the program. When you personally refer (direct sponsored) a new member into the FX Trading Corp opportunity, you will earn 6% of the initial amount they invested as reference bonus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company also offers binary bonus, and career and residual income that use an MLM binary compensation plan structure to pay out these commissions. For Binaries, they have only 2 legs, each leg offers its own points (1 point equals to 1USD) which is counted separately and each leg can have unlimited levels deep which let to fill the levels from both direct and indirect referrals. You will receive a 10% on your small leg that has fewer points and you must have personally sponsored active member on your left and right legs (at least one on each side) to qualify for these commissions.
Also in the residual income, you earn 2% of your entire network which is linked directly to the career plan and based on points you earn, you be qualified to a star level which also offers additional benefits and prizes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;lets-get-started&quot;&gt;Let’s Get Started&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Register with FX Trading Corp&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://platform.investingninja.club/signup-fxtrading-corp&quot;&gt;https://platform.investingninja.club/signup-fxtrading-corp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Select the plan you want to get started with and click “&lt;em&gt;Create&lt;/em&gt;”&lt;/strong&gt;, to see the invoice with amount of Bitcon which is equal to the plan you selected alone with the wallet address.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/post-guide-to-fxtradingcorp/invoice.png&quot; alt=&quot;Investment Invoice&quot; title=&quot;Investment Invoice&quot; width=&quot;250&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Transfer the exact Bitcoin amount to the wallet address&lt;/strong&gt;, and that’s it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BTC amount is equal to the plan (USD amount) you have selected and If you already have BTC, you can directly transfer the amount to the wallet address in the Invoice. Also, If you do not have a BTC yet, you can buy Bitcoins from BlockChain or CoinBase or any other Crypto Trading site you are familiar with. Also you can contact us as well, we can help you to buy BTC’s from a trusted re-seller.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once everything done, You can sit back and check your account balance for the daily profit gains and below is the recent profits for our BOT1000 investment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/post-guide-to-fxtradingcorp/daily-gains.png&quot; alt=&quot;Daily Gains&quot; title=&quot;Daily Gains&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So we hope you had a good understanding of this investment opportunity and as we personally invested on FX Trading Corp, Investing Ninja team personally recommending you to try this out and also as a &lt;strong&gt;High Return Investment, there are also a High Risk is associated&lt;/strong&gt; and what we do recommend is to start with BOT100, BOT300 or BOT500 plans, and if the investment oppourtunity fits your needs and with your own experience, you can then upgrade to a higher plan which suits all your needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good luck, and we are always here to help you throughout your journey!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/guide-to-fxtrading-corp/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/guide-to-fxtrading-corp/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Investment</category>
        
        <category>Cryptocurrency</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Do You also Want to be a Millionaire? </title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We are in the best of times and the worst of times for MLM . . . Jobs are scarce, and many people are facing employment insecurity. Time freedom and income freedom, which used to give us our “sex appeal” as an industry, have shifted in their impact. Regular jobs sometimes offer flex-time, which puts a J-O-B on a par with our industry, and the income freedom that you are seeking has remained elusive for many, where as a salary, however meager it may be, is predictable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ask yourself these questions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where is your company headed? (Mission statement, leadership, integrity issues . . .)
What is your life mission?
Do you have a genuine, trusted role model who exemplifies true devotion to the company and its substance?
Is your “mentor” successful on the level you’re striving for?
Who is your target audience?
How appealing does your product/service appear if you remove the compensation?
What is your basis of emphasis — is it about “you” or “them”?
How are you planning to upgrade your lifestyle when you double your income?
Do you have a clear-cut work program designed to generate your immediate and short-term goals?
Is your belief locked in enough to sustain you through disappointments and setbacks?
Are you willing to learn to lead from the back of the room?
Are you patient?
Answering these questions should give you clarity about what you want and what you’re willing to sacrifice to make it happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beginning this business, you are entering what I call the Bun Syndrome. My husband, Taylor Hegan, and I always have what we refer to as “a lot of buns in the oven.” We’ve got “buns going in” (new distributors), “buns cooking” (beginning builders), “buns browning” (leaders developing) and “buns leaving the oven” (advanced leaders on the way to millionaire status). As we are not in the ‘convincing business,’ we expect our team members to participate in leadership mentoring and follow through with commitments on their own. I want to recommend to you a book that I have gleaned insights from and that has expanded my thinking, The 21 Irrefutable Laws of Leadership by John Maxwell.
Ask yourself one more question, “If you continue to think like you’ve always thought, you’ll continue to get what you’ve always gotten. Is it enough?” As I continue to re-invent myself as an industry leader, I realize that I cannot ask people to do what I am not currently doing, nor can I expect them to exceed the pace I set. Even though we have earned over five million dollars with our company and worked our way to the # 1 distributorship production level, we still execute all the elements of the business and continually field test to see what is effective in today’s marketplace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything works some of the time and nothing works all of the time. We must be ever vigilant to examine ways of expanding when the economy fluctuates. It is imperative that you stay open to breakthrough thinking and give the industry a three-year internship commitment. Then, get ready for the most thrilling time of your life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The MLM business is fun, lucrative, creative, non-discriminatory, rewarding, people-oriented and ever-changing. If you want to attach yourself to a career with no ceiling— you have come to the right place. As a former schoolteacher, I have to pinch myself when I think about the lifestyle that Taylor and I now lead. I make more in a month than I used to make in a year. As you consider your MLM future, remember: “You cannot be anything outside of yourself greater than you are within.” If you truly want to become a millionaire in this business, your own mindset and behavior must reflect financial success. Remember: “likes” attract “likes” and “winners” gravitate toward other “winners.” There is room for you in our MLM winners’ circle if you earn your rightful place by becoming a top producer. It is all about LUCK: L aboring U nder C ertain K nowledge The best part is— you create your own luck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright 2005 Eileen Silva&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/tutorial/2019/06/19/do-you-also-want-to-be-a-millionaire.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/tutorial/2019/06/19/do-you-also-want-to-be-a-millionaire.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We all wait for summer</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This is changed. As I engage in the so-called “bull sessions” around and about the school, I too often find that most college men have a misconception of the purpose of education. Most of the “brethren” think that &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;education should equip&lt;/a&gt; them with the proper instruments of exploitation so that they can forever trample over the masses. Still others think that education should furnish them with noble ends rather than means to an end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems to me that education has a two-fold function to perform in the life of man and in society: the one is utility and the other is culture. Education must enable a man to become more efficient, to achieve with increasing facility the ligitimate goals of his life.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/tutorial/2018/01/12/we-all-wait-for-summer.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/tutorial/2018/01/12/we-all-wait-for-summer.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tree of Codes</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The first mass-produced book to deviate from a rectilinear format, at least in the United States, is thought to be this 1863 edition of Red Riding Hood, cut into the shape of the protagonist herself with the troublesome wolf curled at her feet. Produced by the Boston-based publisher Louis Prang, this is the first in their “Doll Series”, a set of five “die-cut” books, known also as shape books — the other titles being Robinson Crusoe, Goody Two-Shoes (also written by Red Riding Hood author Lydia Very), Cinderella, and King Winter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for this particular rendition of Charles Perrault’s classic tale, the text and design is by Lydia Very (1823-1901), sister of Transcendentalist poet Jones Very. The gruesome ending of the original — which sees Little Red Riding Hood being gobbled up as well as her grandmother — is avoided here, the gore giving way to the less bloody aims of the morality tale, and the lesson that one should not disobey one’s mother.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;It would seem the claim could also extend to die cut books in general, as we can’t find anything sooner, but do let us know in the comments if you have further light to shed on this! Such books are, of course, still popular in children’s publishing today, though the die cutting is not now limited to mere outlines, as evidenced in a beautiful 2014 version of the same Little Red Riding Hood story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An 1868 Prang catalogue would later claim that such “books in the shape of a regular paper Doll… originated with us”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The die cut has also been employed in the non-juvenile sphere as well, a recent example being Jonathan Safran Foer’s ambitious Tree of Codes.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/tutorial/2018/01/12/tree-of-codes.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/tutorial/2018/01/12/tree-of-codes.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Red Riding Hood</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The first mass-produced book to deviate from a rectilinear format, at least in the United States, is thought to be this 1863 edition of Red Riding Hood, cut into the shape of the protagonist herself with the troublesome wolf curled at her feet. Produced by the Boston-based publisher Louis Prang, this is the first in their “Doll Series”, a set of five “die-cut” books, known also as shape books — the other titles being Robinson Crusoe, Goody Two-Shoes (also written by Red Riding Hood author Lydia Very), Cinderella, and King Winter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An 1868 Prang catalogue would later claim that such “books in the shape of a regular paper Doll… originated with us”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;It would seem the claim could also extend to die cut books in general, as we can’t find anything sooner, but do let us know in the comments if you have further light to shed on this! Such books are, of course, still popular in children’s publishing today, though the die cutting is not now limited to mere outlines, as evidenced in a beautiful 2014 version of the same Little Red Riding Hood story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The die cut has also been employed in the non-juvenile sphere as well, a recent example being Jonathan Safran Foer’s ambitious Tree of Codes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for this particular rendition of Charles Perrault’s classic tale, the text and design is by Lydia Very (1823-1901), sister of Transcendentalist poet Jones Very. The gruesome ending of the original — which sees Little Red Riding Hood being gobbled up as well as her grandmother — is avoided here, the gore giving way to the less bloody aims of the morality tale, and the lesson that one should not disobey one’s mother.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/tutorial/2018/01/12/red-riding.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/tutorial/2018/01/12/red-riding.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Powerful things you can do with the Markdown editor</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;There are lots of powerful things you can do with the Markdown editor&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’ve gotten pretty comfortable with writing in Markdown, then you may enjoy some more advanced tips about the types of things you can do with Markdown!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As with the last post about the editor, you’ll want to be actually editing this post as you read it so that you can see all the Markdown code we’re using.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;special-formatting&quot;&gt;Special formatting&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As well as bold and italics, you can also use some other special formatting in Markdown when the need arises, for example:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;del&gt;strike through&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;==highlight==&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;*escaped characters*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;writing-code-blocks&quot;&gt;Writing code blocks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two types of code elements which can be inserted in Markdown, the first is inline, and the other is block. Inline code is formatted by wrapping any word or words in back-ticks, &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;like this&lt;/code&gt;. Larger snippets of code can be displayed across multiple lines using triple back ticks:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;.my-link {
    text-decoration: underline;
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to get really fancy, you can even add syntax highlighting using Rouge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;walking&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;reference-lists&quot;&gt;Reference lists&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The quick brown jumped over the lazy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another way to insert links in markdown is using reference lists. You might want to use this style of linking to cite reference material in a Wikipedia-style. All of the links are listed at the end of the document, so you can maintain full separation between content and its source or reference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;full-html&quot;&gt;Full HTML&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps the best part of Markdown is that you’re never limited to just Markdown. You can write HTML directly in the Markdown editor and it will just work as HTML usually does. No limits! Here’s a standard YouTube embed code as an example:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe style=&quot;width:100%;&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Cniqsc9QfDo?rel=0&amp;amp;showinfo=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/tutorial/2018/01/12/powerful-things-markdown-editor.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/tutorial/2018/01/12/powerful-things-markdown-editor.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is Intelligence Enough</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Education must also train one for quick, resolute and effective thinking. To think incisively and to think for one’s self is very difficult.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;We are prone to let our mental life become invaded by legions of half truths, prejudices, and propaganda. At this point, I often wonder whether or not education is fulfilling its purpose. A great majority of the so-called educated people do not think logically and scientifically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even the press, the classroom, the platform, and the pulpit in many instances do not give us objective and unbiased truths. To save man from the morass of propaganda, in my opinion, is one of the chief aims of education. Education must enable one to sift and weigh evidence, to discern the true from the false, the real from the unreal, and the facts from the fiction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The function of education, therefore, is to teach one to think intensively and to think critically. But education which stops with efficiency may prove the greatest menace to society. The most dangerous criminal may be the man gifted with reason, but with no morals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The late Eugene Talmadge, in my opinion, possessed one of the better minds of Georgia, or even America. Moreover, he wore the Phi Beta Kappa key. By all measuring rods, Mr. Talmadge could think critically and intensively; yet he contends that I am an inferior being. Are those the types of men we call educated?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We must remember that intelligence is not enough. Intelligence plus character–that is the goal of true education. The complete education gives one not only power of concentration, but worthy objectives upon which to concentrate. The broad education will, therefore, transmit to one not only the accumulated knowledge of the race but also the accumulated experience of social living.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/tutorial/2018/01/12/is-intelligence-enough.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/tutorial/2018/01/12/is-intelligence-enough.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Markdown Example</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated. Something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext&lt;/code&gt; and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'Tom'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints 'Hi, Tom' to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com/docs/home&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/tutorial/2018/01/11/markup-example.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/tutorial/2018/01/11/markup-example.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
