<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Investing Ninja</title>
    <description>Invest like a Ninja</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 19:18:23 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 19:18:23 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.5</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Guide to Emergency Fund</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-is-an-emergency-fund&quot;&gt;What is an emergency fund?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you like it or not, things can go wrong in your life and emergency fund is simply money that is enough to get you out of a sudden expense such as car wreck, medical expenses, or a financial crisis such as losing your job. Well, suddenly seeing that new clothing go on 50% clearance sale doesn’t qualify as an emergency. so, we’re talking about money you have saved to get you through true emergencies in life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What if you suddenly lose your job. How are you going to cover your expenses for the next few months? let’s not talk about paying your Netflix bill but electricity, food and gas? The only way is to get in to more and more debits such as credit cards or high-interest loans if you don’t have any savings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just like losing you job, you don’t know what’s going to happen next in your life and it is the reason to have an emergency fund and it will come in handy in many cases, specially it’s a primary step to improve your personal finance as this will eventually help you to get out of your debt and not to get in to more debts even it’s not your best days in life. And also, it’s must to have an emergency fund if you are thinking about financial independence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-much-should-you-save-in-your-emergency-fund&quot;&gt;How much should you save in your emergency fund?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is depending from person to person and there are no any hard and fast rule to figure the amount you need to save, the more stable your income and household are, the less you need in your emergency fund. Recommended strategy is to have at least three to six months of your monthly mandatory expenses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have more than one income source or a stable permeant job, it’s more likely to having a three months fund is more than enough for you but if you got only one income source or a contract or commissions based job, having a six months long fund can save lots of trouble even if you lose your job or get in to a critical illness or anything like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;where-should-you-keep-your-emergency-fund&quot;&gt;Where should you keep your emergency fund?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Key of having an emergency fund is access to the money whenever you are in a true emergency, so funds should be liquid enough to get whenever you need it without much hassle and as fast as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ideally Savings Account or Money Market Account is the ideal account to host the fund but make sure to not to mix it with your regular checking account. If you do so, your fund won’t last long, and it won’t be an emergency fund as whenever you want, you’ll start using that money thinking you’ll settle it later but that later won’t come until you face an emergency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-to-start-building-your-emergency-fund&quot;&gt;How to start building your emergency fund?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;1-figure-out-how-much-you-need-to-save&quot;&gt;1. Figure out how much you need to save&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;It’s not mandatory to deposit your three or six months’ worth fund to the emergency fund at the very first day, If you can do that it’s great but even if you can’t do that, you can simply start building the fund monthly or whenever you have money, but make sure to make it a consistent habit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So as the first thing, identify the amount you need to have in your emergency fund which is only the mandatory expenses for your three- or six-months period. And also, how note down much you going to save monthly for the emergency fund and please come up with a number, that number will help you to stick to the plan in the longer run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;2-open-your-savings-or-money-market-account&quot;&gt;2. Open your Savings or Money Market account&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Create a different account for your emergency fund, else whenever you need money just for additional expenses, you’ll use your emergency fund.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additional monthly expenses and emergency expenses are two different things, so you need to make sure you won’t use your emergency fund to cover up that additional money you have already spent by going out with your friend or doing that extra shopping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;3-automate-it&quot;&gt;3. Automate it&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Pay yourself first, that’s the key to your financial success and make sure to setup a standing order from your savings or checking account to the emergency fund, so that way you won’t miss building your fund ever again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Habit is a powerful thing that make you automate things and keep it going forever without even thinking or worrying, just like that setting up a standing order from your checking/savings account will automate your emergency fund build up process and you don’t even have to think about it or go through the trouble of withdrawing your money and depositing in your emergency account. See, isn’t it simple?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;know-your-emergencies-before-using-your-fund&quot;&gt;Know your emergencies before using your fund&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even though some sudden expense pops up like an emergency, you need to make sure you use your emergency fund only for true emergencies. The life insurance or the additional new cloths you got for your costume contest won’t fit as emergency and anything you know that’s going to occur in future is also not an emergency. so, when a sudden expense pops up, ask following three question to yourself, to see if you really need to use your emergency fund:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Is it unexpected?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Is it necessary?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Is it urgent?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the answer is “yes” to all or at least two questions, more likely it’s a true emergency and you are doing the right thing by using your emergency fund, but always make sure to use your fund wisely as you are already in an emergency and it’s your only emergency fund.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;is-it-all&quot;&gt;Is it all?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now you have an emergency fund and you know you won’t be like the last time you were in real emergency. but just because building the fund won’t make you financially independent or free and you still have to monitor your fund and keep funding it if you ever use your emergency fund for a true emergency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being financially independent is a long journey and starting the habit of saving is known as “paying yourself fist” is a great start towards that better financial future with financial freedom. Also, as you all want to be a good investors and Invest like a Ninja, it’s must to master the habit of savings and building your emergency fund will let you manage your risk factor in the near future. And also, never ever try high risk investments with your emergency savings, it’s only for an emergency and not for the investing. Good Luck!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/guide-to-emergency-fund/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/guide-to-emergency-fund/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Financial</category>
        
        <category>Savings</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
